As times change, difficult cases increase in number!
تتضاعف القضايا المعقّدة مع مضيّ خط الوقت
Today's stage is a villa!
!مسرح اليوم هو منزل أثرياء جبليّ
A black shadow beneath a chandelier!
!ظلّ أسود يتربّص أسفل ثريّا
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
The Wealthy Daughter Murder Case (Part 1).
جريمة قتل الابنة الثريّة (الجزء الأوّل)
Happy birthday!
!عيد ميلاد سعيد
Yotsui Reika (24) Daughter of Yotsui Group President
(24)   يوتسوي ريكا ابنة رئيس مجموعة يوتسوي
Happy 24th birthday, Reika!
عيد ميلاد رابع وعشرون سعيد لك يا ريكا
Thank you, Father!
!شكراً يا أبي
I humbly thank you all for being here today!
أشكركم بإخلاص جميعاً على حضوركم لداري !الجبلي من أجل ابنتي اليوم
May both she and the Yotsui Group continue to prosper!
!أطيب التمنّيات لها ولمجموعة يوتسوي
Stop eating like a pig! You're embarrassing me!
!كفّ عن الأكل بشراهة! أنت تحرجني
Oh, come on! You guys should eat too!
!عليكما الأكل أيضاً
It's not often you see food like this!
فلن تحصلوا على فرصة لتناول طعامٍ هكذا قريباً
Gotta love that vintage wine!
!النبيذ العتيق مميّز حقاً
Now then, allow me to introduce our special guest!
دعوني أقدّم لكم ضيفنا الخاص !الذي دعوتُه اليوم
The great Mori Kogoro-sensei!
!المُبجّل موري كوغورو سينسي
Could I get a box to go?
أيمكنني وضع هذا في علبة؟ سآخذه معي
It'd be a crime to waste any!
فمن الإهدار ترك أيّ بقايا
Mori-san!
!موري-سان
Wow! The modern-day Akechi Kogoro?!
أنت أكيتشي كوغورو عصر هيسي الشهير إذاً؟
You're too kind!
!شكراً لكم! شكراً
The truth is, he helped my daughter just yesterday!
ساعد ابنتي كثيراً في الأمس
Oh, it was nothing!
لم يكن شيئاً يُذكر
What did you do for her?
بمَ ساعدتها
Just a tough little case.
مجرّد قضيّة صعبة صغيرة
A tough case?
قضيّة صعبة؟
I heard about that, Detective Mori!
!سمعتُ عن الأمر أيّها المتحرّي موري
You found Miss Reika's dog, Bubble-chan!
!وجدتَ كلب الآنسة ريكا العزيز، بابل-تشان
It was nothing!
...لم يكن
My name is Ichieda!
أعتذر على عدم التعريف بنفسي، اسمي إيتشييدا
It's a real honor to meet you!
!يشرفني لقاء المتحرّي ذائع الصيت
You're too kind!
أنت تحرجني
Seriously. One look from those sharp eyes
أنتَ مُبهر بحق، رمقة واحدة من عينيك الحادتين
is all it takes to make a criminal confess.
كافية لدفع أعتى المجرمين للاعتراف
The young lady was wise to choose you.
كما تتوقّع من المتحرّي الذي اختارته الآنسة
That's enough, you brown-nosers.
يكفي أيّها المُتملقان
Mifune?!
ميفوني؟
I don't know about you, but he seems like a middle-aged airhead to me.
،ربما تنويان ملاطفة الآنسة
What was that?!
!ماذا قلت؟
How rude!
!يا للوقاحة
He's good!
!فطن
Don't you agree?
ألا توافقني؟
Yes...
بلى
I looked forward to today,
كنتُ متشوّقاً لليوم
but he's not quite what I imagined...
لكنّه لم يكن كما تصوّرت
How dare you!
!كـ-كيف تجرؤان؟
Goes to show how childish you are.
لهذا لا تأخذ بكلام الأطفال
Haven't you heard the saying,
:ألم تسمعا بمقولة الصقر الموهوب يُخفي مخالبه"؟"
Playing dumb to catch an opponent off guard
التظاهر بالسذاجة لمباغتة الخصم
is a preferred tactic of all great detectives.
هي إحدى تكتيكات المتحرّيين العظماء
Isn't that right, Mori-san?
ألستُ على حق يا موري-سان؟
Some tactic.
يا للتكتيك
She anticipated that very fact.
تكهنت الآنسة بذلك
She's really something.
إنّها مُبهرة حقاً
Not to mention beautiful and refined!
!وجميلةٌ وأنيقة فوق ذلك
I wonder who won her heart?
من قد يربح قلبها يا ترى؟
I dunno, but he's gonna be one happy guy.
لا أدري، لكنّه سيكون رجلاً سعيداً
He gets to be the next head of the Yotsui Group!
فسيصبح الرئيس التالي لمجموعة يوتسوي
Bathroom... Bathroom...
حسناً، أين الحمّام؟
This hallway sure is dark...
هذا الرواق مُظلم بحق
Why aren't the lights on?
لمَ لا يضيئون المصابيح؟
Here we go.
حسنٌ
A closet?
خزانة؟
Shower room...
حوض استحمام
Here's the bathroom!
!ها هو الحمّام
Huh? The lights won't turn on.
ماذا؟ الأنوار لا تُفتح
What are you doing there?
أنت! ماذا تفعل عندك؟
I need to use the bathroom...
...أحتاج لاستعمال الحمام
The lights in this washroom don't work;
لا تعمل المصابيح في هذا الحمام
use the one across the way.
استعمل الذي في الجانب الآخر
Okay.
حـ-حسناً
But that's odd. None of the lights around here work.
لكن هذا غريب، لا مصابيح تعمل في الخزانة أو حوض الاستحمام أو الحمّام
I thought I changed them all just recently...
ظننتُ أنّي بدّلتها قبل فترة قصيرة
Sir!
!سـ-سيّدي الرئيس
Your daughter's car has a flat tire!
!هناك إطار مثقوب بسيّارة ابنتك
What?!
!ماذا؟
What should we do?
ما العمل الآن؟
Shall I take you home in my Ferrari?
لا خيار، ما رأيك أن أقلّك بسيارة الفيراري خاصتي؟
No, I'll take you in my Porsche!
كلا، سآخذها بالبورش خاصتي
How about my Benz?
ماذا عن سيارتي البينز؟
Um...
...المعذرة
All three of your cars have flats, too...
إطارات سيّاراتكم مثقوبة أيضاً
Damn it! They got my car too!
تبّاً، إطار سيّارتي مثقوب كذلك
Mine, as well.
وسيّارتي
Who the hell did this?!
!من فعل هذا؟
Dad's rental car seems fine.
يبدو أنّ سيارة أبي المستأجرة بخير
Yeah.
أجل
Six cars have flat tires.
ستّ سيّارات بإطارات مثقوبة
The six of you will have to share cars with--
...سيكون عليكم الستّة مشاركة السيّارة السليمة
No!
!كلا
Today is my birthday!
!اليوم عيد ميلادي
I refuse to be stuffed into someone else's car!
!أرفض مزاحمة الناس في سيارة شخص آخر
Now, now, Reika...
...على هونك يا ريكا
I'm staying here with Yone tonight!
سأبقى هنا مع يوني الليلة
Come send for me in the morning.
أرسل من يقلّني في الصباح
Then I'll stay too.
سأبقى معك أيضاً إذاً
Me too!
!وأنا
And me!
!أنا كذلك
Then I, too, will spend the night and protect her
سأبيت بدوري وأحمي الآنسة
from these young wolves.
من الذئاب الشابة
Good idea. I can rest easy with you on the job.
فكرة حسنة، يمكنني الاطمئنان بوجودك يا روكودا-سان
I leave her in your hands.
أتركها بين يديك
Very good, sir.
حاضر سيّدي الرئيس
Right this way.
لندخل يا آنستي
Fools. Her husband was already decided two years ago.
يا للسُذج، اُختير شريكها منذ عامين
Everyone left?! Then we should go--
...غادر الجميع؟ علينا إذاً
We can't! Not until you sober up!
!لا يمكننا! عليك أن تصحو من ثملك أوّلاً
Yes! Stay a little longer and tell us about your cases!
!صحيح، ابق لفترة أطول وأخبرنا عن قضاياك
Splendid idea.
فكرةٌ حسنة
What do you say we all play cards?
ما رأيكم أن نتسلّى باللعب بالبطاقات جميعاً؟
Count me out.
لا تحسبوني
Detective. I'll drive you home.
حضرة المتحرّي، سأقلّكم لبيتكم
Gimme your car keys.
أعطني مفتاح سيّارتك
Oh, are you leaving?
ماذا؟ أستغادر؟
That's a pity. You were one of my candidate suitors.
هذا مؤسف، فقد كنتَ أحد مرشّحي الزواج بي
I only came here to make sure the deal
أتيتُ هنا اليوم تودّداً لأبيك
between my company and your old man's goes through.
وكي أمهّد تمهيد الطريق للصفقة بين شركتي وشركته لا أكثر
Sorry, but I'm not interested in you.
آسف، لكنّي لست مهتماً بك
Hey now, Mifune!
...ميفوني، أنت
Forget him.
دعه وشأنه
Yeah. The fewer rivals the better.
أجل، تقلّص المنافسين لمصلحتنا
So there you have it, Detective.
هكذا الأمر حضرة المتحرّي
The key, please.
فأعطني المفتاح من فضلك
Yeah...
...أ-أجل
What was that for?!
!ما-ما بك؟
If you want to leave, then leave!
!إذا كنت تريد المغادرة فغادر
But you can say goodbye to your deal!
!لكنّ الصفقة مع شركتك لن تتمّ
You can't be serious!
!مـ-مستحيل
Yone. I'm going to change upstairs.
يوني، سأغيّر ثيابي في الطابق العلوي
Very good.
حسناً آنستي
You're nothing but caged birds.
أنتم مجرد طيور محبوسة في النهاية
You can't survive unless I feed you.
لا تستطيعون النجاة دون أن أطعمكم
You were all members of the same yacht club?
كنتم أعضاءً في نادي اليخت نفسه؟
We used to sail around nearby islands in her boat!
كنّا نبحر في جزيرة مجاورة بقارب الآنسة
Those were great times!
كانت أوقات مُمتعة
They sure were.
كانت كذلك
Until the accident two years ago, anyway!
حتّى وقوع الحادثة قبل عامين
Accident?
حادثة؟
It's old news.
إ-إنّها من الماضي
We promised never to talk about it again!
!اتّفقنا على ألّا نذكرها مجدداً
She certainly is taking a long time...
بالمناسبة، تأخّرت الآنسة
What do you suppose she's doing?
ما الذي عطّلها يا ترى؟
Forget about her.
انسوا أمرها
We don't need her selfish attitude.
لسنا بحاجةٍ لاتّباع أهوائها
Hasn't it been a little too long?
ألم تطل أكثر من المعقول؟
Alright, then.
حسناً إذاً
Sorry, but could you take a look in her room?
المعذرة، لكن هلّا تفقّدتِ غرفتها يا يوني-سان؟
Certainly.
نعم
I'll go check the other rooms.
سأتفقّد بقية الغرف
Then I'll go, too.
سأرافقك إذاً
Me too.
وأنا
Same here.
أنا كذلك
Reika-sama!
!آنستي
That's strange. She isn't anywhere.
هذا غريب، ليست في أيّ مكان
Maybe she left and got lost in the forest?
أيمكن أنها خرجت بمفردها وضلّت في الغابة؟
Our only choice is to split up and search the forest.
لا أمامنا سوى الانفصال والبحث داخل الغابة
What a nuisance.
يا إلهي، يا للآنسة المُتعبة
Reika-sama!
!آنستي
Hey! Where are you?!
!أتسمعين؟ أين أنت؟
Reika-san!
!ريكا-سان
Damn, where on earth did she go?!
تبّاً! أين ذهبت؟
It's starting to come down!
!بدأت تُمطر
What now?
ما العمل؟
Let's go back for now.
لنرجع للمنزل للوقت الراهن
Okay.
حسناً
Huh?
ماذا؟
Isn't that Nikaido-san?
أليس هذا نيكايدو-سان؟
Hey, Nikaido! Hey!
!نيكايدو! أنت
It's no use. He's dead.
لا جدوى، إنّه ميت
What?!
!ماذا؟
He was drowned.
كان سبب الوفاة الغرق
Someone probably held his head in this fountain.
أغرق أحدهم رأسه داخل هذه النافورة غالباً
You can't be serious!
!لا-لا يُعقل
He was alive just a few minutes ago!
!كان حيّاً حتّى قبل لحظات
Yes. Meaning he was killed just now
!أجل! أي أنّه قُتل قبل قليل
by someone near this lodge!
!بيدي أحد قرب هذا المنزل
That's terrible! Who would do such a thing?!
فظيع! من قد يُقدم على أمرٍ كهذا؟
I can think of someone suspicious.
يوجد شخص واحد، الأكثر إثارة للشبهة
The missing Reika-sama!
!إنّها المفقودة، الآنسة ريكا
She would never!
!يـ-يستحيل أن تفعل شيئاً كهذا
No, there's still no telling who.
كلا، لا يمكننا الجزم بعد
For all we know, she could be dead too.
فقد تكون هي مقتولة بدورها
For now, let's call the police.
لنتّصل بالشرطة بأيّ حال
We can talk after that.
سنؤجل الكلام لبعدها
Eh? The phones are out?!
ماذا؟ حرارة الهاتف مقطوعة؟
Yes, all of them!
أجل، كلّ الهواتف
How can that be?!
كيف يمكن هذا؟
Is this the killer's doing?
أهذا من فعل القاتل؟
I'll use my cell phone!
لا خيار، سأستعمل هاتفي الخلوي
Don't bother. There's no phone reception out here.
لا جدوى، هذه المنطقة خارج نطاق الخدمة فلن تستطيع الاتّصال
Our only option now is to use the detective's car.
خيارنا الوحيد الآن هو استعمال سيّارة المتحرّي
Yeah. Someone could take it and get the police...
صحيح، يمكن لأحدنا استقلالها وإخبار الشرطة
Well, now my tires are flat too.
وجدتُ إطارات سيّارتي قد ثُقبت بعدما تحقّقت الآن
Which means someone wants to keep us here.
ما يعني أنّ أحداً يحاول احتجازنا هنا
What the hell?!
!تبّاً! ما هذا؟
We'll just have to wait until the cars come tomorrow.
سيكون علينا انتظار قدوم السيّارات الأخرى صباحاً
Yone-san. Please make us some coffee.
يوني-سان، هلّا أعددتِ لنا بعض القهوة من فضلك؟
Certainly.
حاضر
I'll help you!
!سأساعدك
Hey, Mifune! Where are you going?
ميفوني! أين تذهب؟
The john.
دورة المياه
Then I'll come too.
سأرافقك إذاً
Me too!
!وأنا
I'll get some towels from the washroom.
سأجلب مناشفاً من غرفة الغسيل
Everyone's dripping wet from the rain.
جميعكم مُبللون من المطر
Thanks.
شكراً لك
You sure know this place well, Mister!
أنتَ مُلم تفاصيل هذا المكان يا عمّ
We used to come here a lot.
كنّا نأتي إليه كثيراً
Oh, that's odd.
هذا غريب
What is?
ما الخطب؟
I can't find any sugar.
لا أجد السكّر في أيّ مكان
Could you check up there for me?
آسفة، لكن هلّا تفقدتِ الدواليب العلوية؟
Sure!
حسناً
There's none up here...
لا يوجد هنا
Oh! Here's some!
!ها هو
I forgot we hoarded some five years ago!
!نسيتُ أنّنا خزّنا مجموعةً قبل 5 أعوام
Is that sugar still any good?
هل ذاك السكّر صالح؟
Say, what kind of accident happened at the yacht club
أخبروني، ما الحادثة التي وقعت في نادي اليخت
two years ago?
قبل عامين؟
Don't be stupid. That's got nothing to do with this.
أحمق، لا علاقة لهذا الآن
Before he was killed, Nikaido-san said that
لكن قال نيكايدو-سان قبل أن يُقتل
Reika-sama's husband was decided two years ago.
أنّ شريك الآنسة اُختير قبل عامين
What?!
!ماذا؟
It might have something to do with this.
ربما للأمر علاقة بهذه القضيّة
Yeah. Looks like we'll need you to talk
أجل، يبدو أنّ عليكم فتح الموضوع
about this accident of yours.
موضوع حادثتكم قبل عامين
It happened during a storm. Most unfortunate.
كانت حادثةً مؤسفة، وقعت في يومٍ عاصف
On that day two years ago,
،في ذاك اليوم قبل عامين
we landed on a small island and went off on our own.
رسونا على جزيرة صغيرة وتفرّقنا نلهو
Little did we know a storm was coming.
لم نعلم باقترابِ عاصفة
Nearly everyone escaped back onto the boat,
،تمكن معظمنا من العودة للقارب أثناء العاصفة الرعدية
except for Nikaido and Reika-sama.
باستثناء نيكايدو الذي كان يصطاد، والآنسة على الجزيرة بمفردها
The island was so small that the full tide could submerge it.
كانت الجزيرة صغيرة بحيث تكفي موجة كاملة لغمرها
One of us took a life raft to rescue her.
ذهب أحدنا بطوف نجاة لإنقاذها
We found them half a day later with life vests on,
وجدناهما بعد نصف يوم بسُترتَي نجاة في البحر
but the person who went to get them was never seen again.
لكن لم نجد من ذهب لنجدتهما
Until the drowned body was found three days later, anyway.
حتّى عُثر على الجثّة الغارقة بعد ثلاثة أيام
Who was it?!
من كان ذاك الشخص؟
My granddaughter, Yaeko.
حفيدتي يايكو
Yone-san!
...يوني-سان
She sacrificed her life to rescue Reika-sama.
ضحّت بحياتها لإنقاذ الآنسة
It was probably worth it to her.
كان الأمر ذا قيمة بالنسبة لها غالباً
Well, your coffee's ready!
قهوتكم جاهزة
Thank you!
!شكراً
At any rate, first we need to find Reika-sama.
بأيّ حال، لن نتقدّم حتّى نعثر على الآنسة
Let's split into two groups and check the house again.
لننقسم لمجموعتين ونتفقد المنزل من جديد
But since one of us could be the killer,
،لكن لوجود احتمال أنّ أحدنا القاتل
let's make sure no one gets separated.
فلنحرص على ألّا ينفصل أحدنا
Good idea! It's safer if we watch each other!
فكرة حسنة، سنتجنب الخطر إن حرسنا بعضنا
We'll start once we're done here.
سنبدأ حالما ننهي الشرب
At a time like this?!
جديّاً، في وقتٍ كهذا؟
Sorry, I'm suddenly sleepy...
آسفة، أشعر بالنعاس فجأةً
You must be tired from all that's happened.
لا بدّ أنّك مرهقة من كلّ ما حدث
You can take a nap on this sofa.
يمكنك النوم لفترة على هذه الأريكة
I'll stay with you.
سأبقى معك
Okay...
...حسناً
Find her?
وجدتموها؟
Nope.
كلا
How about you?
ماذا عنكم؟
Not here!
!لا شيء
She doesn't seem to be anywhere.
لم نجدها بعد كلّ هذا البحث
Geez...
...يا إلهي
Reika-sama!
...آنستي
What're you doing?!
ما الذي تفعله؟
Let's move on.
لننتقل للغرفة التالية
Reika-sama!
آنستي
Where'd she disappear to?
أين اختفت؟
Yaeko...
...يايكو
Not in here...
ليست هنا
Or in here.
ولا هنا
That takes care of the first floor.
بحثنا في كلّ الطابق الأوّل الآن
She must be in the forest after all...
لعلّها في الغابة بالفعل
The power's out. Did something happen upstairs?!
انقطعت الكهرباء، أحصل شيءٌ في الأعلى؟
Where's the circuit breaker?
أين القاطع؟
Across from the kitchen.
في اتّجاه المطبخ
What was that?!
ماذا؟ ما كان ذاك الصوت؟
It's close by!
!إنّه قريب
Who shut off the power?!
!من قطع الكهرباء؟
We just got here...
وصلنا لتوّنا بدورنا
It was the killer.
كان القاتل
With us checking the house, they had nowhere to run,
لم يجد مكاناً للهرب مع بحثنا في المنزل
so they cut the power and escaped out this window!
فقطع الكهرباء و هرب
The bastard!
!ذ-ذاك الوغد
You're not getting away!
!لن تهرب
Mifune!
!مـ-ميفوني
Oh no! Stop them!
!كلا! علينا إيقافهما
Damn! Where'd everyone go?!
تبّاً! أين ذهبوا؟
People often get lost in this forest...
يتوه الناس كثيراً في هذه الغابة
Yone-san! What are you doing here?!
يوني-سان! ماذا تفعلين هنا؟
I followed you when you scurried outside!
تبعتكم بعدما هرعتم للخارج
Wait a minute!
!لـ-لحظة
That means Ran's all alone!
!هذا يعني أنّ ران بمفردها
Who is this person?
من هذا الشخص؟
Water?
صوت ماء؟
Ran!
!ران
Hey, Ran! Wake up! Ran!
!ران! أفيقي! ران
Shinichi?!
شينتشي؟
What happened?!
ماذا حصل؟
Someone held my head underwater...
...حبس أحدهم رأسي تحت الماء
But I'm glad you came, Shinichi...
...لكن يسرّني أنّك أتيت يا شينتشي
Ran! Ran!
!ران! ران
Whew, she's just asleep. She had me scared!
نامت فقط؟ لا تخيفيني هكذا
But that's strange.
لكن هذا غريب
This would normally wake a person up.
هجومٌ كهذا كفيل بأن يفيق أحدهم عادةً
Was there sleeping medicine in her coffee?!
أكانت هناك حبوب منوّمة في قهوتها؟
But why Ran?
لكن لمَ ران؟
Huh? Didn't the old man leave this open?
ماذا؟ ألم يترك العمّ هذا المايكرويف مفتوحاً؟
It's warm. How come?
دافئ، لمَ؟
What? Ran was attacked?!
!ماذا؟ تعرّضت ران للهجوم؟
I think someone gave her sleeping pills.
أظن أحداً نوّمها بحبوب تنويم
Sleeping pills?
حـ-حبوب تنويم؟
It was probably in the coffee.
ألم نشرب القهوة جميعاً قبل قليل؟ كانت في قهوتها غالباً
Didn't you and Ran make the coffee?
ألم تعدّي وران القهوة يا يوني-سان؟
But I would never--
...لـ-لكن يستحيل أن
You didn't attack her--
...لم تهاجميها بما أنّك كنتِ
you were in the forest with us.
في الغابة معنا
The fact that she was attacked just because she was here
لكن تعرّضها للهجوم لكونها هنا صدفةً وحسب
means that these might be random murders!
!يعني أنّها قد تكون جرائم قتل عشوائية
You were with her when the power went out, right?
كنتِ معها عندما انقطعت الكهرباء في هذه الغرفة، صحيح؟
Yes.
أجل
Did anything strange happen?
أحصل شيءٌ غريب وقتها؟
There was a warm breeze,
كان هناك نسيمٌ دافئ
and then the lights went out...
ثمّ انطفأت المصابيح فجأة وفقما أظنّ
A breeze?
نسيم؟
The air conditioner?!
!أيمكن أنّه مكيّف الهواء؟
12:30! That's when the power went out!
!الثانية عشرة والنصف! المؤقت على وقت انقطاع الكهرباء
All the air conditioners were set to go on at 12:30!
كلّ مكيّفات الهواء ضُبطت على التشغيل عند الثانية عشرة والنصف
Now I know how the killer cut the lights!
!عرفتُ الآن كيف استدعى القاتل الظلام
The killer is someone in this mansion!
!إنّه أحد الأشخاص في هذا المنزل
It's too dangerous to stay in your room alone!
!لا تفعل! من الخطير أن تبقى في غرفتك بمفردك
He's right, Mifune! It's past 4:00!
صحيح يا ميفوني، تجاوزت الساعة الرابعة
The cars will be here in three hours!
ستصل السيّارات هنا في ثلاث ساعات
Ha! I can't stay with you guys
اخرس! لا يمكنني البقاء معكم
when one of you might be a killer!
!بينما يمكن أنّ القاتل أحدكم
I'll be in my room too.
سأكون في غرفتي أيضاً
We'd all be safest together...
سنكون بأمان أكثر إن بقينا معاً
Where's the bathroom?!
!أين الحمّام؟
The two murders were done the exact same way!
اُرتكبت الجريمتان بالطريقة نفسها تماماً
Was it you?
أكان أنت؟
I didn't do it!
!لم أكن الفاعل
Ichieda-san isn't the killer!
!إيتشييدا-سان ليس القاتل
Mifune-kun. You did it.
ميفوني-كن، أنت الفاعل
Don't be stupid.
لا تكن أحمقاً
The same could be said about you!
!يمكن أن يُردّ الكلام عليك
You're the only one who could've done it!
!أنت الوحيد الذي يمكن أنّه الفاعل
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
"The Wealthy Daughter Murder Case (Part 2)."
جريمة قتل الابنة الثريّة (الجزء الثاني)